Chaluvadi Harshini (1) Featured

Associate with 4+ years of experience in developing chatbots and working experience on AWS Services



Current Designation: Associate Consultant Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Limited Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Information Technology]

Pref. Location: INDIA, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: nodejs, javascript, aws lex, aws lambda, amazon alexa, kore.ai, microsoft bot framework, microsoft luis, azure

app service, google dialogflow, c, c++, html, core java, hadoop,amazon s3,dynamo db,MS SQL,VBA,Macros

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Experience with all phases of Software Development life cycle with Agile Methodology.

Extensive experience on NodeJS, Javascript.

Worked on VCA platforms like Kore.ai, MS Bot Framework and Amazon Alexa.

Worked on NLP Services like LUIS, Dialog flow and Amazon Lex.

Working Knowledge on AWS, Microsoft Azure cloud services.

Trained a custom Speech to Text transcription model in Microsoft Cognitive Service.

Basic Knowledge on Python.

Working knowledge on GIT repository.

Strong analytical and problem solving skills.

Reputation for dedicated teamwork, high energy, work ethics and commitment with capability to handle new technologies and situations.

Has the motivation to take independent responsibility as well as ability to contribute and be a productive team player.

Work Experience

Infosys Limited as Associate Consultant

Jan 2021 to Till Date

Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd as Associate

Nov 2016 to Jan 2021

- Experience with all phases of Software Development life cycle with Agile Methodology.
- Extensive experience on NodeJS, Javascript.
- Worked on VCA platforms like Kore, MS Bot Framework and Amazon Alexa.
- ? Worked on NLP Services like LUIS, Google Dialogflow and Amazon Lex.
- ? Working Knowledge on AWS, Microsoft Azure cloud services.
- Trained a custom Speech to Text transcription model in Microsoft Cognitive Service.
- ? Basic Knowledge on Python.
- ? Working knowledge on GIT repository.
- Strong analytical and problem solving skills.
- Reputation for dedicated teamwork, high energy, work ethics and commitment with capability to handle new

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=16b369699a38afc84b8858fac5fb5d42515c0a581c4009400045455b0c0... technologies and situations.

Has the motivation to take independent responsibility as well as ability to contribute and be a productive team player.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from Osmania University in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Nodejs, JavaScript	
Python	
CORE JAVA	
HTML, CSS	
MS SQL	
Microsoft Visual Studio Code	
ATOM and eclipse	
GIT	
AWS Lambda	
AWS LEX	
Amazon Alexa	
Kore.ai	
LUIS	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Proficient			
Telugu	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: Abbvie Healthcare Bot

Client: AbbVie Inc.

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Dec 2019 - Till Date Project Location: Hyderabad Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Role: Programmer Team Size: 4

Skill Used: NodeJS, Amazon Alexa

Role Description: * Developed the conversational flow using NodeJS.

- Published an AWS Alexa skill for Healthcare Bot by using Alexa Skills Kit SDK using NodeJS and deployed it on AWS
- Training Language model on AWS Alexa
- Designed the language model and tra

Project Details: Description:

The purpose of this Alexa private skill is to respond to Healthcare related queries and displaying the organizational metrics on Amazon echo show device. The Alexa skill has integrations with Healthcare backend APIs using multi-factor

authentication.

Responsibilities:

Developed the conversational flow using NodeJS.

Published an AWS Alexa skill for Healthcare Bot by using Alexa Skills Kit SDK using NodeJS and deployed it on AWS

Training Language model on AWS Alexa

Designed the language model and trained Amazon Alexa accordingly.

Helped automate testing of basic features of the bot.

Worked on botium for testing language model.

Project Title: Toyota Connectivity Issues Bot

Client: Toyota

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Oct 2019 - Dec 2019 Project Location: Hyderabad Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 3

Skill Used: NodeJS, Dialogflow

Role Description: * Designed and developed conversational flow using NodeJS.

Analysed client requirements and identified intents and entities to be trained in Dialogflow.

Project Details: This Bot is able to solve/ provide the guidelines on the connectivity issues while connecting your mobile

phone with car or any other devices.

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time